// This questions are taken from EnglishTestBlog.com
const englishtestblogcomnoun =[ // NOUN
    { // News: Singular or Plural?( May 29, 2024)
        question: "What time _____ on TV?",
        answers: ["is the news", "are the news", "is news", "is the new"],
        correct: "is the news",
        description: "News is an uncountable noun, we treat it as a singular noun in sentences. Thus we use is instead of are."
    },
]
const englishtestblogcomverb = [ // VERB

    
    { // Phrasal Verbs with Look (Jun 2, 2024)
        question: "During her trip abroad, Sarah asked her neighbor to ____ her plants.",
        answers: ["look after", "look down on", "look up to"],
        correct: "look after"
    },
    { // Phrasal Verbs with Look (Jun 2, 2024)
        question: "As a child, I always ____ my older sister because she was so kind and smart.",
        answers: ["looked after", "looked down on", "looked up to"],
        correct: "looked up to",
        description: "Look up to means to admire or respect someone. For example I really look up to my grandmother for all the wisdom she has shared with me."
    },
    { // Phrasal Verbs with Look (Jun 2, 2024)
        question: "It's not nice to _____ people just because they have less money than you.",
        answers: ["look after", "look down on", "look up"],
        correct: "look down on",
        description: "Look down on means to think that you are better or more important than someone else. For example she tends to look down on people who don't have a college degree."
    },
    { // Phrasal Verbs with Look (Jun 2, 2024)
        question: "When my parents go on vacation, I have to _____ my little brother.",
        answers: ["look after", "look down on", "look up to"],
        correct: "look after",
        description: "Look after means to take care of someone or something. For example Can you look after my dog while I'm away?"
    },
    { //Perfecting Your Grammar: Verbs After 'Would Rather' (May 28, 2024)
        question: "She would rather _____ time with her family than go out with friends.",
        answers: ["spend", "to spend", "spending", "spends"],
        correct: "spend",
        description: "After 'would rather' we use a bare infinitive without 'to' We don't use 'would rather' with an -ing form or a to-infinitive and it doesn't change regardless of the subject."
    },
    { //Perfecting Your Grammar: Verbs After 'Would Rather' (May 28, 2024)
        question: "I would rather _____ to the park than stay at home",
        answers: ["go", "to go", "going"],
        correct: "go",
        description: "We use <b>would rather</b> to express a preferring one thing to another. For example<br>I would rather eat at home than go out.<br>She would rather read a book than watch TV.<br>They would rather walk than drive.<br>After 'would rather' we use a bare infinitive without 'to' We don't use 'would rather' with an -ing form or a to-infinitive and it doesn't change regardless of the subject."
    },
    
    
    
]

const englishtestblogcomadjective = [ // ADJECTIVE
{ // Economic or Economical? Do you know the difference between these adjectives? (May 27, 2024)
    question: "It would be more _____ to buy groceries in bulk.",
    answers: ["Economic", "Economical"],
    correct: "Economical",
    description: "Economical means using resources carefully and avoid waste. It is often used to describe actions or things that save money or resources such as being frugal or efficient. For example<br>She is very economical with her spending.<br>Hybrid cars are more economical than traditional gas-guzzlers."
},
{ // Economic or Economical? Do you know the difference between these adjectives? (May 27, 2024)
    question: "LED bulbs are an _____ alternative to traditional incandescent lights",
    answers: ["Economic", "Economical"],
    correct: "Economical",
    description: "Economical means using resources carefully and avoid waste. It is often used to describe actions or things that save money or resources such as being frugal or efficient. For example<br>She is very economical with her spending.<br>Hybrid cars are more economical than traditional gas-guzzlers."
},
{ // Economic or Economical? Do you know the difference between these adjectives? (May 27, 2024)
    question: "The _____ crisis caused widespread job losses.",
    answers: ["Economic", "Economical"],
    correct: "Economic",
    description: "Economic is an adjective that related to the economy, finances or the management of resources. For example<br>The economic policy was designed to reduce inflation.<br>Economic growth is crucial for the development of a country."
},

]

const englishtestblogcomidioms = [// Idioms
    { // Think You Know Idioms? Answer These 3 Questions! (May 26, 2024)
        question: "They threw themselves ______ into the charity event.",
        answers: ["heart and soul", "hand to mouth", "hand in glove"],
        correct: "heart and soul",
        description: "'Heart and Soul' means to be completely engrossed in something."
    },
    { // Think You Know Idioms? Answer These 3 Questions! (May 26, 2024)
        question: "After the paint fight, the kids were splattered with colors from _____",
        answers: ["eye to eye", "head to toe", "hand to mouth"],
        correct: "head to toe",
        description: "Head to toe means completely covering one's body"
    },
    { // Think You Know Idioms? Answer These 3 Questions! (May 26, 2024)
        question: "In terms of customer service, this company stands _____ above the rest.",
        answers: ["head to toe", "hand to mouth", "head and shoulders"],
        correct: "head and shoulders",
        description: "'Be/stand head and shoulders above' means to be much better than other people or things"
    },
    { // Think You Know Idioms? Answer These 3 Questions! (May 26, 2024)
        question: "The detective and the forensic expert worked _____ to solve the mystery",
        answers: ["hand in glove", "eye to eye", "heart and soul"],
        correct: "hand in glove",
        description: "'Hand in glove' closely connected with someone especially in an <b>illegal activity</b>. It is most often used with the verb 'work'."
    },
    
]

const englishtestblogcombasicgrammer = [ // basic grammer
// Ready for a Challenge? Test Your Grammar in Our Mixed Quiz Adventure! (Premiered Nov 22, 2023)
{
    question: "The car broke down, _____ we had to call for roadside assistance.",
    answers: ["so", "although", "because", "but"],
    correct: "so"
},
{
    question: "Harry: \u0022Does your sister work here?\u0022<br>Me: \u0022______\u0022",
    answers: ["Yes, she do", "Yes, she have", "No, she hasn't", "No, she doesn't"],
    correct: "No, she doesn't"
},
{
    question: "Despite the obstacles, _____, I must keep pursuing my dreams.",
    answers: ["somewhere or other", "anyway or other", "somehow or other", "on one way or another"],
    correct: "somehow or other"
},
{
    question: "I'm sorry if I bothered you; I ____ the wrong number while trying to call my sister.",
    answers: ["decoded", "dialled", "directed", "done"],
    correct: "dialled"
},
{
    question: "\u0022Thanks for covering for me at the meeting.\u0022<br>\u0022______; we're part of the same team.\u0022",
    answers: ["Don't mention it", "You mention it", "No mention of it", "You don't mention it"],
    correct: "Don't mention it"
},
{
    question: "She is translating the stories....",
    answers: ["has been written by her brother", "that has ben written by her brother", "what have been written by her brother", "which have been written by her brother"],
    correct: "which have been written by her brother"
},
{
    question: "_____ of these books are on my reading list for this year.",
    answers: ["Everything / Something", "Some / Everything / All", "Every / Some / All", "Both / Some / All"],
    correct: "Both / Some / All"
},
{
    question: "Change the sentence to the passive voice.<br>The coach scolded him for arriving late.",
    answers: ["The coach is scolded for arriving late", "He was scolded for arriving late", "He is scolded for arriving late", "The coach was scolded for arriving late"],
    correct: "He was scolded for arriving late"
},
{
    question: "____ good friends you have!",
    answers: ["How", "How a", "What", "What a"],
    correct: "What"
},
{
    question: "The restaurant's service was ____ than I thought, and the food took forever to arrive.",
    answers: ["worse", "more worse", "worst", "the worst"],
    correct: "worse"
},
{
    question: "_____ andes are ____ longest continental mountain range in the world.",
    answers: ["- / the", "the / -", "the / the", "- / a"],
    correct: "the / the"
},
{
    question: "Ann Accidently _____ the cup when she ____ up",
    answers: ["drops / will wash", "dropped / was washing", "will drop / will wash", "drops / was washing"],
    correct: "dropped / was washing"
},
{
    question: "I much prefer classical music ____ pop music",
    answers: ["than", "over", "on", "to"],
    correct: "to"
},
{
    question: "It is necessary ____ him to do it ____ this year.",
    answers: ["of / in", "to / -", "for / -", "to / by"],
    correct: "for / -"
},
{
    question: "Did you hear a dog ____ in the neighborhood last night?",
    answers: ["barked", "barking", "to bark", "barks"],
    correct: "barking"
},
{
    question: "I saw you _____ the key under the doormat.",
    answers: ["to put", "put", "puts", "will put"],
    correct: "put"
},
{
    question: "Dental problems can arise in children who eat _____ sugar",
    answers: ["few", "a few", "a lot", "a lot of"],
    correct: "a lot of"
},
{
    question: "The car is as ____ as mine",
    answers: ["fast", "faster", "fastest", "the fastest"],
    correct: "fast"
},
// Test Your Language Skills: Can You Nail This Grammar Quiz? (Premiered Nov 20, 2023)
{
    question: "_____ north sea separates _____ British isles from _____ Europe.",
    answers: ["- / the / the", "The / the / -", "The / the / the", "- / the / -"],
    correct: "The / the / -"
},
{
    question: "______ type of tornado can destroy everything on its way.",
    answers: ["The strongest", "Stronger", "The most strongest", "Strongest"],
    correct: "The strongest"
},
{
    question: "The bus will arrive at the station in ______.",
    answers: ["a quarter of an hour", "one quarter of an hour", "a quarter of one hour", "a quarter of hour"],
    correct: "a quarter of an hour"
},
{
    question: "He hurt his leg during practice and sadly, he _____ take part in the competition.",
    answers: ["ought", "couldn't", "could", "won't be able"],
    correct: "couldn't"
},
{
    question: "He reluctantly agreed _____ the group on the mountain hike.",
    answers: ["join", "joining", "to join", "joins"],
    correct: "to join"
},
{
    question: "'Who's that book _____?' 'The author is George Orwell.'",
    answers: ["on", "by", "at", "in"],
    correct: "by"
},
{
    question: "'_____ did you cook for dinner last night?'<br>'I tried a new recipe I found online.'",
    answers: ["what", "when", "who", "how much"],
    correct: "what"
},
{
    question: "What ____ you talk about during the family dinner last night?",
    answers: ["do", "done", "does", "did"],
    correct: "did"
},
{
    question: "I find that reading a book before bed helps me relax and sleep very ____.",
    answers: ["good", "better", "well", "best"],
    correct: "well"
},
{
    question: "Studying for exams can be mentally _____, so taking breaks is essential",
    answers: ["tired", "tiring", "tire", "tires"],
    correct: "tiring"
},
{
    question: "He left ____ school ____ the age of 18",
    answers: ["- / at", "before / of", "for / on", "for / in"],
    correct: "- / at"
},
{
    question: "I wanted to go to the beach, _____ it started raining heavily.",
    answers: ["so", "but", "and", "because"],
    correct: "but"
},
{
    question: "She couldn't attend the meeting _____ she had a doctor's appointment.",
    answers: ["so", "but", "and", "because"],
    correct: "because"
},
{
    question: "He changed his diet _____ the advice of a nutritionist.",
    answers: ["with", "on", "in", "at"],
    correct: "on"
},
{
    question: "I met ____ at the park, and we enjoyed a lonely afternoon picnic together.",
    answers: ["a friend of my", "a friend of me", "a friend of mine", "one my friend"],
    correct: "a friend of mine"
},
{
    question: "'______ did the accommodation cost?'<br>'It was $110 per night.'",
    answers: ["How often", "How many", "How long", "How much"],
    correct: "How much"
},
{
    question: "____ you planning to join the hiking trip?",
    answers: ["Do", "Are", "Is", "Was"],
    correct: "Are"
},
{
    question: "She had read about it ____ the newspaper",
    answers: ["on", "at", "in", "for"],
    correct: "in"
},


]


const englishtestblogcommiscellaneous = [ // miscellaneous

    // How Well Do You Really Know English? Take the Quiz Now! ( Dec 25, 2023 )
    {
        question: "She was completely blind _____ the faults for her children.",
        answers: ["of", "for", "on", "to"],
        correct: "to",
        description: "Blind to something means 'not noticing or realizing something'"
    },
    {
        question: "She's feeling overwhelmed with the workload but she won't ______ to avoid appearing incapable.",
        answers: ["tell so", "say so", "tell", "say"],
        correct: "say so",
        description: "We use 'so' after certain verbs of thinking and speaking to avoid repeating a positive clause.<br>She won't say so = She won't say she's feeling overwhelmed with the workload."
    },
    {
        question: "Despite the unexpected setbacks, the team decided to keep calm and _____ with the project.",
        answers: ["bring up", "come on", "carry on", "call for"],
        correct: "carry on",
        description: "The phrasal verb 'carry on doing something' means to continue doing a specific action or activity."
    },
    {
        question: "The contract expires in six months or when the projects is completed, ____ happens first.",
        answers: ["however", "whatever", "whichever", "whenever"],
        correct: "whichever",
        description: "'whichever happens first' means that out of two or more events or situation, the one that occurs earlier in time will be the one that matters or is relevant."
    },
    {
        question: "Our lawn is getting quite long; we should _____ this weekend.",
        answers: ["have our grass cut", "got cut our grass", "got our grass to cut", "have to cut our grass"],
        correct: "have our grass cut",
        description: "We usually use 'have something done' when we are talking about playing someone to do something for us. It's often used for services. The form is subject + have + object + past participle"
    },
    {
        question: "We ______ taken a map; now we're lost in the city.",
        answers: ["could have", "should have", "might have", "may have"],
        correct: "should have",
        description: "'should have' is used to express regret or a missed opportunity"
    },
    {
        question: "Choose the correct synonyms",
        answers: ["prudent - careless", "hazard - assurance", "tolerance - prejudice", "destructive - damaging"],
        correct: "destructive - damaging"
    },
    {
        question: "We never expected our peaceful town to be a site for ______ terrible things.",
        answers: ["such", "such a", "so", "so much"],
        correct: "such",
        description: "we use 'such' + adjective + uncountable noun or phural noun"
    },
    {
        question: "She decided to wears the red dress to the party, and it really _____ her",
        answers: ["fits", "matches", "suits", "hangs"],
        correct: "suits",
        description: "'suits' is commonly used when referring to clothing that compliments or looks good on someone."
    },
    {
        question: "_____ must have been something bad in the news because everyone in the office seems concerned.",
        answers: ["It", "There",],
        correct: "There",
        description: "We say 'there' to say that something exists somewhere"
    },
    {
        question: "After the divorce, Mark now lives _____ in a small house by the lake.",
        answers: ["by himself", "himself", "his own", "him"],
        correct: "by himself"
    },
    {
        question: "Which word is a correct past simple verb?",
        answers: ["runned", "fleed", "catched", "gripped"],
        correct: "gripped",
        description: "others except 'gripped' are not correct past test form. These are ran, caught and fled"
    },
    
]